救救我
Help me!
伊甸湖
你能玩藏猫猫吗
Can you play at peek-a-boo?
我能玩藏猫猫
I can play at peek-a-boo!
你能看见我吗 是的 我能
Can you see me? Yes, I can.
藏猫 藏猫 藏猫猫
Peek-a-peek-a-peek-a-peek-a-boo!
做得好 非常棒 现在 嘘
Well done. That's very good. Now, ssh!
坐好
Still.
大家起立
And everyone up.
这周的课结束 好样的
And that's the end of the week. Well done.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
抱歉
Sorry.
凯特的男朋友带她去巴黎过周末
Kat's boyfriend is taking her to Paris for the weekend
我男朋友却带我去废弃的猎场
and mine is taking me to a disused quarry!
是个被淹没的猎场 相信我 很可爱
It's a flooded quarry. Trust me. It's lovely.
在开发商把那建上楼前
It's the last chance to see it
这是最后一次机会了
before the developers build over it.
前方有测速摄像头
'Speed camera ahead.'
好样的 凯丽      你真是个孩子
Good on you, Kylie.        You're such a boy!
这点可以用我的手机来弥补 它很性感吧
And I can mate it up to my mobile phone. Pretty sexy, huh?
停下 我在开车呢
Stop it, I'm driving.
那是什么
What's that?
这家伙的老婆背不好 很奇怪对吧
The guy's wife had a bad back. Kinky, huh?
事实上 挺舒服的
Actually, it's quite nice.
你想让我停车吗
Do you want me to pull over?
下午好 你一直在谈无力的家长
'Good afternoon. You've been talking about fining parents
他们不能控制自己孩子的行为
'who fail to control their children's behaviour.
这种政策什么时候实行的
'When was the policy introduced? '
学会尊重是05年大选
'As you probably remember The Respect Agenda
的重要议题
was a big issue in the last election at 2005.
布莱尔想把尊重的思想
'Tony Blair wanted to bring back a sense of respect
带入学校与社区
'in schools and communities.'
所以提高给家长的资助
'So increase the amount of support for parents,
包括与家长签订合同
'including parenting contracts,
让家长去参加如何为人父母的课程
'to get parents to attend parenting classes.'
这个问题是... 这是你的问题 你来解决
'It's a case of... "It's your problem, you sort it."
没有学校支持 这难以做到
'It's hard to do without the school behind you.
...不愿去学校
'...struggling to school as well
我家的8岁孩子也不愿去学校
'I have an 8-year-old struggling to school as well.'
让你的孩子去上学 这是少数人的做法
'Get your kids to school This is a tiny minority and
孩子需要学东西
children need to be in school in order to learn,
这很关键
that is crucial.
然而 早期的干预不够迅速来...
'However, the early intervention isn't as quick to... '
这种被处罚的局面很难被扭转
'It's hard to turn it over, being fined.
孩子们从中学不到任何东西
Kids are not learning anything by that.
他们知道我们会付钱的 所以他们会提起
'They know we're going to pay so they gonna mention it.
他们觉得很高兴
They find it hilarious.
在报纸上读到他们...
'You know, reading about themselves in the papers... '
就在这附近
It's up here somewhere.
在十字路口处左转
'At the traffic lights, turn left.'
上帝啊
Jesus!
到了 有啤酒 床和早餐
Here it is. Beer, bed and breakfast.
太好了
Perfect.
不是吧
No way!
抱歉
Excuse me?
酒吧的气氛不错
Great bar presence!
要点什么
Ey up, me duck?
请来两品脱啤酒
Two pints of lager, please.
还给我 还给我 还给我
Give it back, give it back, give it back!
他们应该上床了 对吧
A bit past their bedtime, isn't it?
是的 小东西们一定累坏了
Yeah, poor things must be exhausted.
小孩需要个好的...
That child needs a good...
我他妈告诉你了
I bloody told you!
再来一点吗
Another pint of Wife-Beater?
好的
Yep.
你就怎么当妈妈的      你怎么
Call yourself a mother?        You what?
你想要牛肉吗 你想要牛肉吗
You want beef, eh? You want beef?
你这个小杂种 你想要牛肉吗
You fucking dickhead! You want beef?
去告诉他们闭嘴      你去说
Go and tell them to shut up.        You tell them.
你是什么 男人还是老鼠
What are you? A man or a mouse?
听着 我上次来还挺好的
Look, it was all right the last time I was here.
跟你的潜水器具一起被气死了吗
Pissed up with your dive buddies?
我向你保证 那他妈的猎场很好
I promise you, the quarry's fucking stunning.
猎场很好
The quarry's stunning.
别说粗话
No "fucking".
拜托 小姐
Please, Miss?
一有路口就左转
'At your first opportunity, turn left.'
伊甸湖 他妈的 斯莱普顿猎场
Eden Lake, my arse! Slapton Quarry!
"设栅栏区域" 他们害怕谁
"Gated community"? Who are they so afraid of?
每个人
Everyone.
越来越浪漫了
This is getting more and more romantic.
你带我到了建筑工地
You've brought me to a building site!
听着 你相信我好吗
Look, will you just trust me?
这儿以前是公共公园 看这儿
This used to be a public park. Look at this.
我们到了
Here we go.
有机会就掉头
'At your first opportunity, turn around.'
有点信仰好不好
Oh, ye of little faith!
你怎么想
What do you think?
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
我看得出来
I can see it.
你好      嘿
Hello.        Hey!
你是骑自行车来的?      没有凯丽的指导
Have you cycled all the way here?        And no Kylie!
你骑的什么车 履带式吗
What have you got there? A caterpillar?
我妈妈说不要跟陌生人说话
My mum says I shouldn't talk to strangers.
你妈妈说得对 我们走吧
Your mum's quite right. We'll leave you to it.
来
Come on.
是的 你看 这儿少了50座房子
Yes, you see, it is missing 50 executive homes.
我喜欢这儿
I love it.
这是新的吗
Is that new?
是的 你喜欢吗
Yeah. Do you like it?
我喜欢底裤 我不确定上面怎样
I like the bottom. I'm not so sure about the top, though.
你他妈的在这儿干嘛      滚开
What the fuck are you doing here?        Clear off!
这是怎么回事      该死的小杂种
What the fuck's all this shit?        Fucking little prick.
嘿 是我们看到的那个小男孩
Hey, that's the little boy we saw.
你什么时候支持英格兰队了
Since when did you support England?
小傻逼
Little hoods.
这个 马克 看
Here, Mark, watch this.
史蒂夫
Oh, Steve...
只是男孩逞能而已
It's just boys being boys.
只要他们别烦我们就好
As long as they leave us alone.
快跑
Run for it, run!
妈的给我滚      去抓住他
Get the fuck out of here!        Go on, have him.
上帝啊
Jesus!
邦妮 来
Bonnie, come!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
好丫头 好丫头
Good girl, good girl, good girl.
来
Come on then.
挺好
Lovely.
想在它把水弄脏之前去泡一泡吗
Fancy a dip before it craps in the water?
不 你去 我看着东西
No, you go. I'll keep an eye on the stuff.
也许是个好主意
Probably not a bad idea.
好丫头
Good girl.
哦 伙计
Oh, man!
来 邦妮
Come on, Bonnie! Bonnie!
邦妮 过来 丫头 过来
Bonnie, come here, girl! Come here! Come here!
好丫头 邦妮
Good girl, Bonnie.
伙计们 能帮我们个忙把音乐关小吗
Hey, guys. Can you do us a favour and turn the music down?
听不见你 伙计      把音量关小
Can't hear you, mate.        Turn your sounds down.
听不见 伙计
Can't hear you, mate.
你在做什么      看好你的狗
What are you doing?        And watch your dog.
他吓着我女朋友了      是她
He's scaring my girlfriend.        She.
贱人 她是个贱人
Bitch. She's a bitch.
别跟傻逼似的 海滩很大
Come on, guys. Don't be dicks. This is a big beach.
有足够的空间给每个人
There's room for all of us.
你叫谁傻逼
Who are you calling a dick?
你在看什么 我的奶头吗
And what are you looking at? My tits?
妈的滚一边去 疯子
Fucking jog on! Prick.
畜生
Dickhead.
嘿 真是个疯子
Hey, what a prick!
妈的
Mug!
我们为什么不再找个地方呢
Why don't we just find another spot?
我不能被一群12岁的小孩吓住了
I won't be bullied by a bunch of 12-year-olds.
那就让这事毁了我们的下午?
And let it ruin our afternoon?
我们先来的
We were here first.
这就让人舒心了
Well, this is relaxing
你在做什么      滚开
What are you doing?        Fuck off!
为什么 为什么
Why? Why?
伙计 我喜欢偷窥
Oh, mate, I love bird-watching.
你喜欢什么 奶头吗      奶头是你
What's with you, you tit?        You're the tit!
你看她干什么
What are you looking at her for?
我没看她的脸 看她的奶头
I'm not looking at her face, just her tits.
她是个丑婊子
She's an ugly bint.
是的 想要我签名吗
Yeah, do you want my autograph?
现在开心了吗
Happy now? Hmm?
嘿 珍妮
Hey, Jenny!
快了
Nearly!
想再喝点啤酒吗
Fancy another brewski?
是的 为什么不呢
Yeah, why not?
史蒂夫 那是什么
Steve, what's that?
没什么
It's nothing.
天黑后没什么可做
There's not much to do after dark.
是的
Nope.
想看看专属于我们的新英格兰之家吗
Wanna check out our exclusive New England home?
当然
Sure.
你喜欢吗      我觉得很漂亮
Do you like it?        I think it's beautiful.
史蒂芬・泰勒
Stephen Taylor...
那是什么声音
What's that noise?
风声而已
It's just the wind.
不 不是风声
No, that's not the wind.
可能是狐狸
Could be a fox.
或者驴子
Or a donkey.
不 听着 嘘
No, listen. Ssh!
是你的想象
You're just imagining it.
我去看看      不 别走 去吧
I'll go take a look.        No, don't go... Go.
史蒂夫
Steve?
有人吗
Hello?
史蒂夫
Steve?
有人吗
Hello?
史蒂夫
Steve!
Steve?
史蒂夫 别添乱了
Steve, stop messing around!
史蒂夫
Steve!
吓死我了      抱歉
That was horrible.        I'm sorry.
走开      真对不起
Get off!        I'm really sorry.
你冻透了      那就暖暖我
Ow! You're freezing!        Then warm me up.
你就是个爱尔兰大大大傻子
You're a big, crude, pikey oaf!
我爱你 爱你
I love you. Love you.
我真的快饿死了
I am absolutely starving.
我可以吃下一匹马      那就去法国吧
I could eat a horse.        So move to France.
我操
Fuck!
妈的
Shit!
怎么了      小杂种们
What's happened?        Little fuckers!
你的轮胎怎么样 伙计      滚一边去
How's your tyre, mate?        Fucking git!
小杂种们
Little fuckers!
不 等等 史蒂夫
No, wait, Steve!
当心      妈的
Watch it!        Shit!
你块头应该小点 该死的蠢蛋
You should've got a smaller body, fucking dollar boy!
要吃早饭吗      我操
Breakfast?        Fuck!
好的 你想要什么
Right, what would you like?
全套英国早餐 加白吐司和咖啡 谢谢
The full English with white toast and coffee. Thanks.
你呢      一样的
And for you?        I'll get the same.
你有没有见到一群
Hey, you wouldn't have seen a bunch of kids
骑自行车的孩子
tooling around on BMXs, would you?
当然了 他们烦到你了吗
Certainly have. Been terrorising you?
是骚扰我们      小恐怖份子
Well, hassling us.        Little terrors.
你这样的大男孩 不必担心的
I wouldn't worry too much, a big boy like you.
他们戳破了我的后轮胎
They punctured my back tyre.
我想应该告诉父母
I thought parents might want to know.
不是我的孩子
Not my kids.
不 我不是说他们是你的孩子
No, I didn't mean they were your kids.
不是我的
Not mine.
算了
Never mind.
我不想惹麻烦
I don't want any trouble.
你在交朋友吗
Making friends?
我想她喜欢我
I think she likes me.
怎么回事
What the?
别 史蒂夫 这没必要
No, Steve, it's not worth it.
如果人人都这么说 我们的处境会怎样
If everyone said that, where would we be?
我一会儿回来
I'll be back in a minute.
有人吗
Hello?
有人在家吗
Anyone home?
有人吗
Hello?
快开走 你挡我道了      好的
Come on, you're blocking my drive!        OK.
快点      好的
Come on!        All right!
抱歉
Sorry!
蠢婊子
Stupid bitch!
妈的
Shit!
布莱特 是你吗 现在就给我下来
Brett! Is that you? Get down here now!
你跑不了的 小兔子
Can't run away, little bunny.
是的 你跑不出来因为你在笼子里
Yeah, that's right, you can't because you're in a box.
布莱特 别让我上去
Brett! Brett, don't make me come up there!
妈的
Shit!
布莱特
Brett!
应该把笼子毁了 烧了它
The hutch should be destroyed. Burn it.
布莱特
Brett!
我们走
Let's go!
我能感到你又像老师一样看我了
I can feel that schoolteacher look.
是的 你很幸运 你可能弄坏什么东西的
Yeah, you're lucky. You could have broken something.
我们享受周末吧      好的 我喜欢
Let's just enjoy the weekend.        Yeah, I'd like that.
好吗
Yes?
你不要说点什么吗      一句也没
You were going to say something?        No, not a word.
你确定吗      是的 我确定
Are you sure?        Yeah, I'm sure.
因为我想你在看我的脚
Because I thought you were looking at my foot.
不 等等 不要
No, wait. No, no!
你要进去了     史蒂夫 别
You're going in!        Steve, no!
不要
No!
真他妈的冷      注意语言
Oh, it's fucking freezing.        Language!
好吗 懒虫
All right, lazy bones?
在湖底能找到这种东西真惊人
It's amazing the stuff you find at the bottom of the lake.
史蒂夫 海滩包在哪儿
Steve, where's the beach bag?
就在这儿
It was right here.
不敢相信 车钥匙在里面
I don't believe it. It's got the car keys in it.
上帝啊 请别告诉我
Please, God, don't tell me...
我操
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
杂种
Tossers!
你还好吗      是的
Are you OK?        Yeah.
珍妮 快点
Jenny, come on.
拜托      不 我们别管了
Come on.        No... Let's just leave it.
车在他们那儿
They've got our car.
来啊来啊
Go on, go on. Go on!
该死的混帐 滚开
Fucking shitting itself! Fuck off!
布莱特
Brett!
听着 我不管你们要在这儿干什么
Listen... I don't care what you're up to here.
我只想要回我的车
I just want my car back.
不是我们干的 伙计
It's not us, mate.
车钥匙 手机 钱包
Car keys, phone, wallet.
不是我们 伙计      史蒂夫 得了 别管了
Not us, mate.        Steve, come on. Let's leave it.
你戴着我的墨镜      是我的 伙计
You're wearing my shades.        They're mine, mate.
你的雷凡飞行镜吗
Your Ray-Ban Aviators?
假的 伙计
Fakes, mate.
是的 史蒂夫 算了
Yeah, Steve, come on.
听着 你们已经玩够了
Listen... You've had your fun.
我们就此作罢 告诉我车在哪儿
Let's just call it quits. Tell me where the car is.
让那畜生退后
Keep that animal back.
我的车在哪儿      我不知道 伙计
Where's my fucking car?        I've got no idea, mate.
看住你的疯狗     看住你的
Watch that fucking dog!        Watch yours!
你说什么
What did you say?
那是我的手机
That's my phone.
史蒂夫      你手机铃声也跟我一样吗
Steve...        Got the same ringtone as me?
史蒂夫
Steve!
打他 他有把刀
Hit him! He's got a fucking knife!
邦妮
Bonnie...
邦妮 邦妮
Bonnie! Bonnie!
你捅死了我的狗
You stuck my dog.
这是意外 给我车钥匙
It was an accident. Give me the car keys.
我送她去看兽医
I'll drive her to the vet.
得了 走吧
Come on, let's go.
滚开
Fuck off!
她 她要死了
She's... She's fucking dying.
对不起
I'm sorry.
她要死了      布莱特
She's fucking dying!        Brett...
布莱特      滚开
Brett...        Fuck off!
邦妮 别离开我 不要 邦妮
Bonnie, don't die on me. Not you. Bonnie!
史蒂夫
Steve...
我拿到钥匙了 快走
I've got the car keys. Let's just go.
得了      别离开我 邦妮
Come on!        Don't die on me, Bonnie!
得了 史蒂夫
Come on, Steve!
邦妮
Bonnie!
快点 快点
Come on, come on.
抓住他们
Get 'em!
我操
Fuck!
史蒂夫 快点
Steve, quick!
好的
Right!
妈的
Shit!
快倒回去
Go back!
妈的
Shit!
上去      上帝啊
Get on to it!        Jesus Christ!
快点
Come on!
快倒车
Quick, go back!
给我下车
Get out the fucking car!
我的上帝 上帝啊      我操
Oh, my God, oh, my God!        Fuck!
给我下车
Get out the fucking car!
该死的杂种
Fucking prick!
我的天哪 妈的
Oh, my God! Shit!
你这个臭婊子      史蒂夫
You fucking bitch!      Steve!
我看不见 妈的我什么都看不见
I can't see, I can't fucking see.
妈的我看不见前面的路 上帝啊
I can't see where we're fucking going! Jesus Christ!
妈的
Shit!
你没事吧 等等
Are you all right? Wait.
我找不到...      我被卡住了
I can't get...        I'm stuck!
我他妈被卡住了
I'm fucking stuck!
等等      上帝啊
Wait.         Jesus!
我找不到      好的 听我说
I can't get it.        OK... Listen to me.
我的天哪 他们来了      听我说
Oh, my God, they're coming!        Listen to me!
听着 快跑 找条路 拿着这个
Listen. Go. Find a road. Take this.
不要      去找人帮忙 快跑
No...        Go get help! Go!
宰了他们
Fucking kill 'em!
这边 这边 快点
This way, this way, come on!
布莱特 在这儿
Brett, it's over here!
我操
Fuck!
过来 我找到车了
Come over here. I've got the car!
布莱特 搞砸了
Brett, this is fucked up!
现在是晚上 到城里有10英里
It's ten fucking miles into town in the dark.
她又不是小姑娘 快没时间了
She's not fucking Lassie! It's out of the time, blood man.
你在看路吗
Are you watching the road?
谁都不准回家 你给我过来
No one goes home. You get here now!
放了我 我什么也不会说的 拜托 放了我
Please, let me go. I won't say anything. Please, let me go.
听着 布莱特 朋友都知道我们在这
Listen, Brett, people know that we're here.
他们会报警的
They're going to call the police.
如果放了我 我发誓 我不会告诉任何人的
If you let me go, I swear on my life, I won't tell anyone.
听着 伙计们 求你们了
Look, guys, come on, please.
我们可以停止的 目前还没有人死
We can stop this. Nobody's died yet.
但我的狗死了
My fucking dog died though!
抱歉 那是意外
I'm sorry. It was an accident.
那是意外
It was an accident.
等我找到你的贱人
There's going to be another accident
会再发生一起意外的
when I find that bitch of yours!
"还没有人死" 等到我看到她
"No one's died." Wait and see what happens to her
等着瞧她会怎样
when I fucking see her!
妈的放开我 小兔崽子
Get the fuck off me! Fucking little prick!
别冲动 好吗
Let's not be head-loose, right?
你说谁冲动      我们别急
Who are you calling head-loose?        Let's not be rash.
他看到的第一个电话 110 是谁冲动
First phone he sees, 999 - who's fucking head-loose?
不 这是胡扯 我从没碰过他
No, this is rash shit, man. I never touched him.
怎么 你没碰他      是的 伙计
What, you didn't touch him?        No, mate.
那你现在就碰
You fucking touch him now then!
他或者我
Him or me.
你想上前 表现得像个男人样吗
You wanna front, you wanna act like the fucking big man?
现在就上
You'll step up now.
好的
All right.
上帝啊
Jesus...
佩吉 拿着这个
Paige, get this!
妈的别拍下来 伙计
Don't fucking record it, man.
不要 等等
No, wait.
妈的等等
Fucking wait!
现在就去      你去死吧
Go on then.        Fuck you!
不 还不够 割得再深一点
No. That's not even a proper cut. Deeper.
深一点
Deeper!
我操
Fuck!
好的 现在 每人来一刀 马奇・马克
All right, now everyone'll have a dig. Marky Mark?
上帝啊
Jesus!
伙计 我见不了这场面      上帝啊
Oh, man, I can't fucking see this!        Jesus!
真他妈的      快上 马克
Fuck's sake.        Go on, Mark.
上帝啊 该死的杂种
Jesus Christ, fucking bollocks.
里奇・迪奇
Ricky Dicky...
来吧
Go on.
妈的 我的鞋子
Shit! My shoe!
有金边的呢 伙计 新的
These are fucking Gold Tops, man. Brand-new.
你这个小杂种
You little fuckwit.
库珀 来吧 伙计 到你了
Cooper! Bang on, mate, you're up!
怎么
What?
来吧 伙计
Come on, mate.
刀子
Knife.
佩吉 都拍下来
Paige, keep that phone up.
是的 每个人都来
Right, Coops, everyone has a dig.
来吧 库珀 看你多有胆
Go on then, Cooper. Let's see your bottle.
快点 快点
Come on, come on. Please.
布莱特 我不能
Brett, I can't.
看在上帝面上 听着 我们在一条船上 快点
For fuck's sake, listen! We're all in this together. Go on.
拜托 他很害怕      我才不怕
Come on. He's only a little scared.        I'm not scared.
听着 他知道我们所有人的名字
Listen. He's heard all of our fucking names.
不这么做他就会报警
Either do it or he's gonna spill.
快点
Go on...
快点 把他的舌头切掉
Do it! Cut his fucking tongue out!
真他妈的 是血      真狠
Fucking hell! That's bloody.        That's lethal.
给你      我不敢相信你做了
Here you are.        I can't believe you did that.
看 是唐尼・马塔那(《疤观煞星》黑帮头领)
Look - it's Tony Montana!
好的 现在我们得结束这一切
All right. Now we've got to finish this.
拜托 拜托
Please, please...
拜托 拜托 拜托
Please, please, please.
拜托
Please...
怎么了
What's up?
蓝牙 她就在这儿
Bluetooth. She's fucking here.
珍妮 快跑
Jenny, run! Run!
快点 快跑
Come on! Run!
那贱人在那儿
There's the bitch!
贱人
Bitch!
去他妈的自行车 快点
Well, fuck the bikes. Come on!
我操
Fuck!
到空地那去 看着那个混蛋
Get to the clearing. Guard the fucker.
好的
Right.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
妈的
Oh, shit!
布莱特 他不见了      什么
Brett, he's gone!        What?
他不在这儿
He's not here!
伙计 他受了伤 走不了多远 跟着血迹走
Mate, he's cut to fuck. Ain't going too far. Follow the blood.
快点
Come on!
操他妈的
Fuck's sake!
奥依 奥依
Oi! Oi!
史蒂夫      珍妮
Steve!         Jenny...
快点 我们要离开这儿
Come on! We've got to get out of here!
快点
Come on...
Come on.
快点
这边
This way.
慢慢躺下 好吗
Gently! All right?
我没事      那就好
I'm all right.        That's it.
好的 要给你清理干净好吗
OK. We're going to clean you up, all right?
给你清理干净
We're going to clean you up.
喝点水
Drink some water.
我
I'm...
做得好 好的
Well done. All right.
好的 会很疼的
OK, this is going to sting.
好
OK...
好样的 我知道会很疼
Well done. I know it does sting.
他妈的      看起来怎样
Oh, shit!        How does it look?
不如看上去那么糟      让我看看
It looks worse than it is.        Let me see.
上帝啊 是黑血 肠子里的血
Oh, Jesus! God! That's black blood. Gut blood.
我他妈会流血而死的      你不会死的
I'm fucking bleeding to death!        You're not going to die!
我不会让你死的 不会的
I'm not going to let you die! I'm not!
他们没刺中动脉
They haven't hit any arteries.
好的 你要冷静下来
Right. You've just got to stay calm.
冷静 你不能激动
You have to stay calm. You can't go into shock.
深呼吸 慢慢来 躺好
Deep breaths, measured breaths. Stay still.
你会没事的 你会好起来的
You're going to be all right. You'll be all right,
没事的 我保证
you'll be OK. I promise.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
对不起 我不知道该怎么办
I'm so sorry. I didn't know what to do.
我想去非洲度蜜月
I thought Africa for a honeymoon.
先去海滩休息一下
Beach first, for a rest,
接着去旅行
and then safari.
只要跟你在一起 去哪儿都好
I don't care where we go as long as I'm with you.
非洲听起来不错
Africa sounds lovely.
我还问过你爸爸
I even asked your old man.
妈的
Shit!
另一边
Other side.
妈的
Ah... shit.
是他 他来过
That's him. He's been here.
找到他 弄死他
Find him and drain him like a fucking bottle.
我累了 布莱特      闭嘴 蠢猪 是不是
I'm tired, Brett.        Shut up, shite bag. Is that you?
是你吗 死胖子
Is that you, fat lad?
不 不是我的 伙计      那是女人的脚印
No, not mine, mate.        That's a girl's footprint.
那她就跟他在一起
Well, she's with him, then.
那混蛋走不远的
That fucker can't be far.
他快死了 大家分头找
He's nearly half fucking dead. Listen to me. Split up.
在这儿和围墙上都有血 好的 快走
Spread out between here and the fence. All right, come on.
你这个死胖子
You fat fuck!
快走 减减肥 你这头猪
Come on. Get going. Work off some of that weight, you fat shit.
抱歉
Sorry...
好样的 把头放低
Well done. Let's get your head down.
就是这样 做得好
That's it, that's it. Well done. Well done.
史蒂夫
Steve?
史蒂夫 史蒂夫 拜托
Steve! Steve, please...
我们要出去 好吗
I've got to get us out of here. OK?
我动不了      那我去 好吗
I can't move.        Then I've got to go. OK?
我在这儿很安全
I'm safe here.
他们走了
They've gone.
你需要血 史蒂夫 否则你会死的
You need blood, Steve, or you're going to die.
我要到城里去
I need to get to town.
我来的时候看到有路标
I saw power pylons on the way in.
肯定能通往城里
They must lead somewhere.
听着
Look.
Look!
你要藏好 要坚持住
Now you stay hidden... and you hold on.
你会回来的
You come back.
布莱特 我真的累了
Brett, I'm really tired.
吸口这个 你这小子
Take a toke on this, you little shit!
快点
Come on!
上帝啊
Aaaaaiee! God!
God!
奥依 是这条路 对吗
Oi, oi, oi! This way, yeah?
快点
Come on!
没事的
It's OK! It's...
是我 我是珍妮 我们在湖边见过的
It's me. It's... It's Jenny. Remember me from the lake?
我 我需要帮助
I just... I need some help.
我要跟你妈妈谈谈 你能带我去找她吗
I want to talk to your mum. Can you take me to her?
她在工作
She's working.
但我...
But I'm...
我真的要进城去
I really need to get into town.
能拜托你带我去吗
Can you please just show me the way?
等等 我们为什么不跟着路标走
Wait. Shouldn't we follow the power lines?
不用 这条路快一点
No, this way's quicker.
我妈妈来这儿接我
My mum picks me up down here.
什么 在这儿吗 她开车载你的自行车吗
What? Here? In her car with your bike?
什么
What?
在这儿有信号吗      没有 玩游戏
Have you got a signal here?        No, just games.
她应该一会儿就来了
She should be here soon.
你不是说她在上班么
I thought you said your mother was working.
她刚和人换完班
She's finished her shift.
没信号吗      只有一格
No signal?        One bar.
亚当 我要用你电话      为什么
Adam, I need your phone.        Why?
我要报警      我们不该来
To call the police.        We shouldn't be here!
拜托      电量很低
Please!        Its battery's low!
没关系 就一会
It doesn't matter. I only need it for seconds.
我妈妈可能要打回来
My mum might need to call me back!
亚当 你妈妈要来接你 是不是
Adam, your mum is coming to get you, isn't she?
亚当 怎么回事
Adam, what's going on?
这儿是哪儿 请告诉我 亚当
Where have you brought me? Please, Adam!
拜托 把这鸟电话给我
Please... just give me the bloody phone!
小母牛 你好啊
How now brown cow!
她醒了 布莱特 她他妈的醒了
She's awake! Brett, she's fucking awake!
马克 你这个娘们 你打得不够狠
Mark, you fucking pussy! You didn't hit her hard enough!
我操
Oh, fuck!
我们找到他了
We found him.
布莱特 我们不能这么做 她还活着
Brett, we can't fucking do this! She's alive!
但他死了
And he's dead.
是我们干的
We did him.
佩吉把你们的所为
Paige has got you every last one you
都拍下来了
fucking move all having a dig.
在她手机上 现在不能退出了 伙计们
It's on her phone. No ballsing out now, lads.
没退路了
No backing down.
上帝啊
Oh, Jesus...
佩吉 拍下来 过来      操他的
Paige, get filming. Come here.        Oh, fuck it!
看着我 伙计 想加入我们吗
Look at me, man. Wanna be in our gang?
那就证明你自己
Prove yourself, then.
请不要 亚当 请别这么做
No, please...! Adam, no, please... don't do it!
请不要 拜托
Please, don't do it! Please...!
快点 继续
Go on. Go on.
怎么      听着 你看到的太多了
What?        Listen, you've seen too much.
你要么下手 要么下一个就是你
You either do it now, yeah, or you're next.
那就快点
Go on, then.
快点
Go on!
不要
No! No-o-o!
住手
Stop!
真他妈的臭
That fucking stinks.
妈的给我看着 下手的是你
Fucking look at that! Fucking that was you.
是你 不是我
That was fucking you, not me.
是你      拜托
Fucking you.        Please...!
死婊子 问她暖不暖和
Fucking bitch. Ask her if it's warm.
暖不暖和 说出来 暖和不
Is it warm? Say it! Is it warm?
是你做的 问她
Fucking you do it an' all! Fucking you all! Ask her!
暖和不 暖和不      说出来 大声点
Is it warm? Is it warm?        Say it! Louder!
暖和不
Is it warm?
烧吧 烧死你这臭婊子 快点
Fucking burn! Burn, you little bitch! Go on!
是的 他妈的 笑吧 孩子 你喜欢的
Yeah! Fucking hell! Fucking smile, boy. You fucking love it.
奥依 奥依
Oi, oi!
来啊
Go on, then.
过来 你这贱人
Come here, you fucking shit!
你要不回来我就烧死他
You get the fuck back here or I'll burn him!
快点 快点
Come on! Come on!
好的 烧死他
Right! Do him!
救命 珍妮 救命
Help! Jenny, help!
救命 救命
Help! Help!
救命
Help!
好的      布莱特 这边
OK...        Brett, this way!
她有地图 她知道路了
She's got the fucking map! She knows which way to go.
不 我们知道她要走哪条路
No, we know which way she's fucking going.
有条小路通到城里
There's one track into town.
她步行走不远的      看
She won't go far on her foot, will she?        Look.
什么 上面怎么说
What? What does it say?
珍妮・格林格拉斯和史蒂夫・泰勒被袭击
"Jenny Greengrass and Steve Taylor attacked.
马克 布莱特 里奇 库珀
"Mark, Brett, Ricky, Cooper."
妈的 我们出名了 伙计
Shit, we're famous, mate!
你有火柴吗      没有 伙计
You got a match?        No, mate.
那就去他的
Fuck it, then.
我发誓 等我找到那个贱人
I swear. When I find that fucking bitch,
我他妈要埋了她 伙计
I'm going to fucking bury her, mate.
真他妈的
Fucking hell!
小混蛋 走
Little prick, come on.
小姐
Miss...
我受不了了
I can't stand it...!
不要
No...!
不 不
No, no, no!
在夜里我们找不到她
We're not going to fucking find her in the dark!
是的 正是 给我继续找
Yes, we fucking are! Go on!
布莱特
Brett!
佩吉      布莱特
Paige?        Brett!
布莱特      佩吉
Brett!        Paige?
看看你他妈做了什么 我操
Look at what you've fucking done! Fuck!
你知道 布莱特 去他妈的 我要走了
You know what, Brett? Fuck this - I'm gone, mate.
什么
What?
不不不 佩吉 电话
No. No, no, no. Paige, phone.
看哪 看看看看 是你 那是你
Look! Look, look, look. Look, look, it's you. That's you.
我不想这样 我不想杀了他
I didn't want this. I didn't want to fucking kill him
我不想烧死那个孩子
or fucking burn that lad ever!
我也不想进监狱      监狱
And I don't want to go to pen.        Pen?
你知道监狱啥样么
What do you know about pen?
你进去过吗 你老头进去过吗
Have you been inside? Has your old man been inside?
你他妈在哭什么 你这娘娘腔
What the fuck are you crying for, you fucking girl?
你在打给谁
Who you calling?
给我放下 给我放...
Put that down. Put that...
给我放下 放下 放下
Put that down. Put it down. Put it down.
给我放下
Put it down.
布莱特      我要打死你
Brett!        I'll fucking batter you!
我要打死你
I'll fucking batter you!
布莱特
Brett...!
我 告诉你 给我 放下
I... told... you... to... put... that... down!
混蛋 混蛋 混蛋
Fucker! Fucker! Fucker! Fucker!
关掉 关掉 关掉
Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off.
给我关机 关机 你这死婊子
Turn it off! Turn it off, you fucking bitch!
天哪 你还好吗      你要帮我
God! Are you OK?        You've got to help me!
拜托 带我离开这儿      操 出什么事了
Please, just get me out of here.        Fuck! What's going on?
求你 帮帮我 他们杀了我男朋友
Please, just help me. They killed my boyfriend and kill you!
带我离开这
Just get me out of here.
好的好的 上车
All right! All right! Get in the car!
发生什么事了     他们在追我
What happened back there?        I'm being hunted.
追你 谁      一个帮派 送我进城
Hunted? By who?        A gang. Just get me into town.
那在另一边      什么叫在另一边
Town's the other way.        Why the other way?
我弟弟在这儿 他应该早回家了
Me fucking brother's out here! He's supposed to be home.
你弟弟?      我弟弟 现在我很担心
Your brother?        My little brother. Now I'm worried.
哦不      里奇
Oh, no...        Ricky?
里奇 你还好吗 你准备好了吗
Ricky, are you OK? You ready?
我一会儿回来 好吗
I'll be there in two ticks. Yeah?
不要 别往这开 掉头
No, please, stop! Turn around!
请走那条路      我会的
Please, go the other way!        I will.
我操 他们最好没事
Fuck! They better be OK.
里奇
Ricky?
里奇 你这个小混蛋 你在哪儿
Ricky? Ricky, you little shite! Where are you?
小杂种 我还有别的事要做
Little bastard! I've got better things to do.
妈妈担心死了
Mum's worried sick.
她说有人在追她 你知道这事吗
This lady says she's been hunted. You know about this?
# 请相信我 我们不会永远被尊重 #
# Please believe us We ain't ever gonna be respectable
# 喜欢我们 讨厌我们 但你会... #
# Like us, hate us, but you'll... #
来人哪 救救我
Somebody, please help me!
# 尊重 尊重 #
#... respectable, respectable... #
别光站着
Don't just stand there!
带她进屋      那就来吧
Get her in the house.        Come on, then.
你的经历很惨      出什么事了
You've been through the wars.        What happened?
别急 慢慢说
Take your time.
拜托 给她点新鲜空气
Come on, give her some air.
真臭 谢谢 唐
That stings, sorry. Thanks, Tan.
我们把她放在这儿
Yeah. We'll put this down here.
你现在安全了      有很多臭男人在
You're safe now.        Lots of big ugly men around.
我还在强叔叔这儿
I'm still at Uncle Jon's.
有个女人冲进来 跟死了一样      梅
A woman crashed in, looking like death.        Mel!
戒指挺漂亮 你男人给的吗
That's a lovely ring. From your fella?
怎么回事
What's that?
嘿 克林迪 进来 低下 出去
Hey, Clyde! Come here! Down! Out!
你在捣乱 我听不见你
You're breaking up. I can't hear you.
抱歉 他对陌生人不友好
Sorry. He's no good with strangers.
梅 梅 怎么了
Mel? Mel, what's going on?
怎么回事 那是里基的车
What the fuck?! That's Reece's van!
快点 告诉我      我要杀了他
Go on, tell me!        Bustard! I'll fucking kill him!
等等      把电话给我
Hang on...        Give me the fucking phone!
帮我叫救护车     强
Get me an ambulance.        Jon?
强 叫救护车 给她叫救护车
Jon, get an ambulance. Get this lady an ambulance.
我要找警察      不不 别担心 亲爱的
I want the police.        Eh? No, no, no. Don't worry, love.
我们会打的 你呆在这就好
You let us do that. Just stay here.
你坐好了      我要吐了
Ssh. You just sit quiet.        I'm going to be sick.
我带你去厕所 来吧 跟我走 亲爱的
I'll get you to the loo. Come on. Come with me. Come on, love.
在这儿 我们到了
In here. Here we go.
李・崔维特 出去
Lee Trevitt! Get out!
真是抱歉
Sorry about this.
出去 来吧 亲爱的
Get out! Go on, love.
哦 上帝
Oh, God...
哦 上帝啊 上帝啊
Oh, God. Oh, God...
快点开门
Open the fucking door!
开门
Open it up!
快开门
Open the fucking door!
就是她吗      是的
Is this the lady?        Yeah.
你这个人渣 我要杀了你
You fucking slag! I'll fucking kill you!
好了 亲爱的
Come on, love!
他说了什么 他是骗子      车是怎么回事
What's he told you? He's a liar!        What about the van?!
我只是想逃命 他们杀了史蒂夫
I was just trying to get away. They killed Steve!
你背叛了你那混蛋男朋友
Yeah. You sell out your sick bastard boyfriend!
不 快报警 报警
No. Just call the police! Call the police.
报警? 他们会怎么收拾她
Call the police? What good are they to her?
我操
Fuck!
你现在想跟大男孩玩玩吗
You want to play with the big boys now?
强 强
Jon... Jon...
她杀了她的儿子
She killed her little one.
看着她 你他妈的看着她
Look at her. You fucking look at her now!
你他妈一直看着她      他们还是孩子
You fucking keep looking at her.        They're just children!
只是孩子 他们只是孩子
Just children! They're just children!
我也不想的...
I didn't mean to...
是他们挑的头      那我们来结束一切
They started this!      And we're gonna finish it.
听着 有孩子死去了 伙计
Look, there's dead kids, man.
警察会过来 他们会问起的
The police will be round here. The police will ask questions.
那他们也找不到答案 不是么
Doesn't mean they'll get any answers, does it?
这里是我们说了算
We look after our own round here.
现在带布莱特去睡觉      不要
Now... Now take Brett to bed.        No...
布莱特 现在上楼去 你这小杂种
Brett, get upstairs now! You little bastard!
现在上楼去
Get upstairs now.
请不要
Please, don't...!
把她放到浴缸里
Just put her in the shower.
不
No-o-o!